Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 68, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 68, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Sweating in Birmingham and district bakeries, 1910; Publication (Box 68, Folder 100)
    Author: Birmingham Trades Council
- Box: 68, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 68, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Take over the mines!: the case for nationalisation, 1944; Publication (Box 68, Folder 101)
- Box: 68, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 68, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Taxation and the worker, Publication (Box 68, Folder 102)
    Author: R. Neft
- Box: 68, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 68, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Tebbit's Bill - kill it!, 1982; Publication (Box 68, Folder 103)
    Author: Mick Costello
- Box: 68, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 68, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Temporary grants for wives, dependent husbands and children, 1921; Publication (Box 68, Folder 104)
    Author: Great Britain, Ministry of Labour
- Box: 68, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 68, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Terms of settlement in the districts: 1926-27, 1927; Publication (Box 68, Folder 105)
- Box: 68, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 68, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Tests for an explicit religion of labour, 1919; Publication (Box 68, Folder 106)
    Author: Charles Gore
- Box: 68, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 68, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Texts adopted by the Second International Conference of Metal & Engineering Workers: Vienna, July 3-7, 1954, Publication (Box 68, Folder 107)
    Author: Trade Unions International of Metal and Engineering Industries
- Box: 68, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 68, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: The Thomson battle, 1926; Publication (Box 68, Folder 108)
    Author: National Society of Operative Printers and Assistants (Great Britain)
- Box: 68, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 68, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: The three enemies, 1919; Publication (Box 68, Folder 109)
    Author: J.A. Seddon
- Box: 68, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 68, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Time for more in the pay packet, 1955; Publication (Box 68, Folder 110)
    Author: Sam Henderson
- Box: 68, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 68, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: To engineers: and other wage slaves, 1920; Publication (Box 68, Folder 111)
    Author: John Owen, Tom Mann
- Box: 68, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 68, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: To intimidate: according to the definition given in Section 3, Subsection 2, Trades Disputes and Trades Union Bill, 1927; Publication (Box 68, Folder 112)
    Author: National Almalgamated Union of Shop-Assistants, Warehousemen and Clerks
- Box: 68, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 68, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: A trade board at work, 1912; Publication (Box 68, Folder 113)
- Box: 68, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 68, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: The Trade Boards Act of 1909 explained, 1910; Publication (Box 68, Folder 114)
    Author: J. R. Brooke
- Box: 68, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 68, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Trade Boards Acts, 1909 and 1918, 1923; Publication (Box 68, Folder 115)
- Box: 68, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 68, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Trade parliaments, why they should be formed and how to form one in your trade, 1919; Publication (Box 68, Folder 116)
    Author: Industrial Reconstruction Council (Great Britain)
- Box: 68, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 68, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Trade union administration, 1929; Publication (Box 68, Folder 117)
    Author: A.W. Petch
- Box: 68, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 68, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Trade union education today, 1961; Publication (Box 68, Folder 118)
    Author: J.P.M. Millar
- Box: 68, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 68, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: The trade union movement and the government, 1968; Publication (Box 68, Folder 119)
    Author: George Woodcock
- Box: 68, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 68, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Trade union problems & policy, 1916; Publication (Box 68, Folder 120)
- Box: 68, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 68, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Trade unionism, 1907; Publication (Box 68, Folder 121)
    Author: H.B. Lees Smith
- Box: 68, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 68, Folder 122)
  - Item 1: Trade unionism: some problems and proposals, 1933; Publication (Box 68, Folder 122)
    Author: Harold E. Clay
- Box: 68, Folder: 123, Publication (Box 68, Folder 123)
  - Item 1: Trade unionism and political action, Publication (Box 68, Folder 123)
- Box: 68, Folder: 124, Publication (Box 68, Folder 124)
  - Item 1: Trade unionists: what next?, 1948; Publication (Box 68, Folder 124)
- Box: 68, Folder: 125, Publication (Box 68, Folder 125)
  - Item 1: Trade unions: the new reality: the communist view, 1986; Publication (Box 68, Folder 125)
    Author: Pete Carter
- Box: 68, Folder: 126, Publication (Box 68, Folder 126)
  - Item 1: Trade unions and common ownership, 1943; Publication (Box 68, Folder 126)
    Author: Common Wealth (Political party)
- Box: 68, Folder: 127, Publication (Box 68, Folder 127)
  - Item 1: Trade unions and the general election, 1945; Publication (Box 68, Folder 127)
- Box: 68, Folder: 128, Publication (Box 68, Folder 128)
  - Item 1: Trade unions and Vietnam: the story of the First British Trade Union Delegation to Vietnam: (an eye-witness account), 1970; Publication (Box 68, Folder 128)
    Author: Jack Jones
- Box: 68, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 68, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in a Labour Britain, 1947; Publication (Box 68, Folder 129)
    Author: James B. Jefferys
- Box: 68, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 68, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in communist countries, 1951; Publication (Box 68, Folder 130)
    Author: Lucjan Blit
- Box: 68, Folder: 131, Publication (Box 68, Folder 131)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in the new democracy: Poland, 1947; Publication (Box 68, Folder 131)
    Author: British-Polish Friendship Society
- Box: 68, Folder: 132, Publication (Box 68, Folder 132)
  - Item 1: Trade unions under socialism, 1932; Publication (Box 68, Folder 132)
- Box: 68, Folder: 133, Publication (Box 68, Folder 133)
  - Item 1: The tragedy of toil, 1912; Publication (Box 68, Folder 133)
- Box: 68, Folder: 134, Publication (Box 68, Folder 134)
  - Item 1: Trades-unionism: the blight on British industries and commerce, 1877; Publication (Box 68, Folder 134)
    Author: John Honeyman
- Box: 68, Folder: 135, Publication (Box 68, Folder 135)
  - Item 1: The training of apprentices on special building work, 1944; Publication (Box 68, Folder 135)
- Box: 68, Folder: 136, Publication (Box 68, Folder 136)
  - Item 1: The Truth about the New Zealand compulsory industrial concilation and arbitration act, 1898; Publication (Box 68, Folder 136)
    Author: W.J. Shaxby, F.G. Ewington
- Box: 68, Folder: 137, Publication (Box 68, Folder 137)
  - Item 1: Two Durham miners in Russia, 1954; Publication (Box 68, Folder 137)
    Author: Thomas auld, National Union of Mineworkers, British-Soviet Society
- Box: 68, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 68, Folder 138)
  - Item 1: UCS - the fight for the right to work, 1971; Publication (Box 68, Folder 138)
    Author: Alex Murray
- Box: 68, Folder: 139, Publication (Box 68, Folder 139)
  - Item 1: Unemployed women and the slave bill, 1934; Publication (Box 68, Folder 139)
- Box: 68, Folder: 140, Publication (Box 68, Folder 140)
  - Item 1: Unemployed workers!: who are your enemies?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 140)
- Box: 68, Folder: 141, Publication (Box 68, Folder 141)
  - Item 1: Unemployment: its cause and the cure: Mrs. Mary Citizen, John Citizen and Mr. Commonsense discuss the problem, Publication (Box 68, Folder 141)
    Author: Thomas Dickson
- Box: 68, Folder: 142, Publication (Box 68, Folder 142)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the distressed areas: labour's smashing indictment of the "National government", 1935; Publication (Box 68, Folder 142)
    Author: Arthur Greenwood
- Box: 68, Folder: 143, Publication (Box 68, Folder 143)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the tasks of the Communists, 1931; Publication (Box 68, Folder 143)
    Author: O. Piatnitsky
- Box: 68, Folder: 144, Publication (Box 68, Folder 144)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the wage fund, 1910; Publication (Box 68, Folder 144)
    Author: James Ramsay MacDonald
- Box: 68, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 68, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Unemployment assistance guide, 1936; Publication (Box 68, Folder 145)
    Author: G. Grant McKenzie
- Box: 68, Folder: 146, Publication (Box 68, Folder 146)
  - Item 1: The unemployment bill and women in industry, 1934; Publication (Box 68, Folder 146)
- Box: 68, Folder: 147, Publication (Box 68, Folder 147)
  - Item 1: The Union of Post Office Workers, Publication (Box 68, Folder 147)
    Author: Union of Post Office Workers (Great Britain)
- Box: 68, Folder: 148, Publication (Box 68, Folder 148)
  - Item 1: Union-smashing by law, 1924; Publication (Box 68, Folder 148)
- Box: 68, Folder: 149, Publication (Box 68, Folder 149)
  - Item 1: Unite for democracy, 1937; Publication (Box 68, Folder 149)
    Author: John A. Mahon
- Box: 68, Folder: 150, Publication (Box 68, Folder 150)
  - Item 1: United action: the only way, 1934; Publication (Box 68, Folder 150)
- Box: 69, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The value of trade unions to the state, 1911; Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Box: 69, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Ventilation and heating: lighting and seeing, 1943; Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Author: Great Britain. Industrial Health Research Board
- Box: 69, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Ventilation of factories and workshops, 1920; Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Author: Great Britain. Home Office
- Box: 69, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Victimisation: an analysis showing its relation to Spencerism & Mondism, 1929; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Author: National Miners Minority Movement (Great Britain)
- Box: 69, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The wage price freeze swindle, 1971; Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Author: Les Evans, Linda Jenness
- Box: 69, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Wages against housework, 1975; Publication (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Author: Silvia Federici
- Box: 69, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Wages and prices in the U.S.S.R., 1946; Publication (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Author: Reginald Bishop
- Box: 69, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Wages and the cost of living: Sir John Anderson answered, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 8)
    Author: William Gallacher, Emile Burns
- Box: 69, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Wages increase for engineering workers, 1953; Publication (Box 69, Folder 9)
    Author: Syd Abbott
- Box: 69, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Wages productivity and training: with special reference to the chemical industry: report, 1951; Publication (Box 69, Folder 10)
    Author: Bob Edwards
- Box: 69, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Wages, prices and profits, 1948; Publication (Box 69, Folder 11)
    Author: Walter G. Stevens
- Box: 69, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The war and the workers, 1939; Publication (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Box: 69, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: War and the workers: a plea for democratic control, 1915; Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Box: 69, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: War and the working class: the Socialist Party states the case, 1936; Publication (Box 69, Folder 14)
    Author: Socialist Party of Great Britain
- Box: 69, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The war and the workshop, 1940; Publication (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Box: 69, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The way to industrial unity, 1919; Publication (Box 69, Folder 16)
    Author: Geo J. Wardle
- Box: 69, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The WEA and adult education, 1953; Publication (Box 69, Folder 17)
    Author: R.H. Tawney
- Box: 69, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The W.E.A. and the trade union movement, 1936; Publication (Box 69, Folder 18)
    Author: Arthur Pugh
- Box: 69, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Welfare and welfare supervision in factories and workshops, 1919; Publication (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Box: 69, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Welfare at work, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 20)
    Author: Therle Hughes
- Box: 69, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Welsh coal industry, 1948; Publication (Box 69, Folder 21)
    Author: David Jeffrey Davies, H.P. Richards
- Box: 69, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: West Cumberland: report of the Labour party's Commission of inquiry into the distressed areas, 1937; Publication (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Box: 69, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: West Indian workers in Great Britain, 1942; Publication (Box 69, Folder 23)
    Author: West Indian workers in Britain
- Box: 69, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: What are these Soviet trade unions?, 1955; Publication (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Box: 69, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: What has already been done, 1895; Publication (Box 69, Folder 25)
- Box: 69, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: What I saw in the iron-works, 1901; Publication (Box 69, Folder 26)
    Author: Edward J. Purslow
- Box: 69, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: What is independent working-class education?, 1920; Publication (Box 69, Folder 27)
    Author: Plebs League (Great Britain)
- Box: 69, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: What is rationalisation?, 1928; Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
- Box: 69, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: What the working people want: the cure for unemployment, 1912; Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
    Author: Moya Llewelyn Davies
- Box: 69, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: What's wrong in the engineering industry?, 1920; Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Box: 69, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: What's wrong with domestic service?, 1930; Publication (Box 69, Folder 31)
- Box: 69, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: What's wrong with the unions?: a syndicalist answer, 1955; Publication (Box 69, Folder 32)
- Box: 69, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: When we make again, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 33)
    Author: D. Hurst
- Box: 69, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Who pays for the attacks on labour?, 1921; Publication (Box 69, Folder 34)
    Author:
- Box: 69, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Who will do the dirty work?, 1952; Publication (Box 69, Folder 35)
    Author: Tony Gibson
- Box: 69, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Why Britain needs a strong labour movement, 1943; Publication (Box 69, Folder 36)
    Author: Betty Reid
- Box: 69, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Why is she away?, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 37)
- Box: 69, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Why not nationalise?, 1957; Publication (Box 69, Folder 38)
    Author: John Gollan
- Box: 69, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Women and the factory acts, 1896; Publication (Box 69, Folder 39)
    Author: Beatrice Webb
- Box: 69, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Women in offices ..., 1936; Publication (Box 69, Folder 40)
    Author: Industrial Women's Organisations (Great Britain)
- Box: 69, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Women in industry, Publication (Box 69, Folder 41)
    Author: Joan Thomson
- Box: 69, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Women, work and trade union organisation, 1980; Publication (Box 69, Folder 42)
    Author: Judith Hunt and Shelley Adams
- Box: 69, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: The Women's Co-operative Guild, 1920; Publication (Box 69, Folder 43)
    Author: Women's Co- operative Guild
- Box: 69, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The work of trade boards, 1913; Publication (Box 69, Folder 44)
    Author: L.V. Lester- Garland
- Box: 69, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Work, trade and taxes, 1923; Publication (Box 69, Folder 45)
    Author: E.G. Brunker
- Box: 69, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Worker democracy: the Labour Party Outline Policy, Publication (Box 69, Folder 46)
- Box: 69, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: The Workers' Charter, Publication (Box 69, Folder 47)
- Box: 69, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Workers' control and self-government in industry, 1933; Publication (Box 69, Folder 48)
    Author: G.D.H. Cole and W. Mellor
- Box: 69, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 69, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Workers' education in Great Britain, 1945; Publication (Box 69, Folder 49)
    Author: Workers' Educational Association
- Box: 69, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 69, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Workers in chains, 1976; Publication (Box 69, Folder 50)
    Author: South African Congress of Trade Unions
- Box: 69, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 69, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Workers of the world!, 1953; Publication (Box 69, Folder 51)
    Author: World Federation of Trade Unions
- Box: 69, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 69, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Workers!: Freedom or servitude?, 1941; Publication (Box 69, Folder 52)
- Box: 69, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 69, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: The workhouse system, 1909; Publication (Box 69, Folder 53)
    Author: Oxford University Branch; Christian Social Union (Great Britain)
- Box: 69, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 69, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Working class income and expenditure, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 54)
    Author: University of Oxford. Institute of Statistics
- Box: 69, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 69, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The working classes and religion, 1913; Publication (Box 69, Folder 55)
    Author: J. Parton Milum
- Box: 69, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 69, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Working conditions in Soviet industry, 1954; Publication (Box 69, Folder 56)
- Box: 69, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 69, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Working women! war is coming!, 1930; Publication (Box 69, Folder 57)
- Box: 69, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 69, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Workmen's compensation: the act explained, 1898; Publication (Box 69, Folder 58)
    Author: Edmond Browne
- Box: 69, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 69, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: The young workers and the general stirke, 1926; Publication (Box 69, Folder 59)
    Author: Young Communist League (Great Britain)
- Box: 69, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 69, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Youth and industry, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 60)
    Author: R.S. Swift
- Box: 69, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 69, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Footnote on the French Miner's Strike, 1963; Publication (Box 69, Folder 61)
    Author: International Federation of Christian Trade Unions
- Box: 69, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 69, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Labor condemns Trotskyism, 1938; Publication (Box 69, Folder 62)
    Author: Confederacion de Trabajadores de Mexico
- Box: 69, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 69, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Manifesto of leaders of the intellectual life of Great Britain on Ireland, 1921; Publication (Box 69, Folder 63)
- Box: 69, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 69, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Ripping off the working class, 1972; Publication (Box 69, Folder 64)
    Author: League for Proletarian Socialism
- Box: 69, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 69, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Skandinavisk sangbok, upplysning, 1930; Publication (Box 69, Folder 65)
    Author: Industrial Workers of the World; Organisation Frihet
- Box: 69, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 69, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Le mouvement cooperatif des employes d'etat dans le Royaume de Yougoslavie, 1937; Publication (Box 69, Folder 66)
- Box: 69, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 69, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Regulations of the working birgades of the People's Youth of Yugoslavia, 1948; Publication (Box 69, Folder 67)
    Author: Peoples Youth of Yugoslavia
- Box: 69, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 69, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: ICFTU subversion in Africa, 1965; Publication (Box 69, Folder 68)
- Box: 69, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 69, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Soviet Russia: a description for British workers, 1935; Publication (Box 69, Folder 69)
    Author: Charles Philips Trevelyan
  - Item 2: Labor condemns Trotskyism, 1938; Publication (Box 69, Folder 69)
- Box: 70, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: CER, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Author: Centro de Estudios de la Revolucion
- Box: 70, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Author: International Transport Workers Federation
    Notes: Ano.3:no.81
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.82
  - Item 3: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.83
  - Item 4: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.84
  - Item 5: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.86
  - Item 6: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.87
  - Item 7: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.88
  - Item 8: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.89
  - Item 9: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.90
  - Item 10: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.3:no.93
  - Item 11: Boletin de Noticias, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.94
  - Item 12: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.95
  - Item 13: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.96
  - Item 14: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.97
  - Item 16: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.98
  - Item 17: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.99
  - Item 18: Boletin de Noticias, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.100
  - Item 19: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.101
  - Item 20: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.102
  - Item 21: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.4:no.104
  - Item 22: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.105
  - Item 23: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.107
  - Item 25: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.108
  - Item 26: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.109
  - Item 27: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.110
  - Item 28: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.116
  - Item 29: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.117
  - Item 30: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.119